<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <item>
            <title>Help us help you...</title>
            <link>/assets/img/change_log/update5.png</link>
            <description>
                When you are saying something isn't working, actually tell us what section isn't.
                Cause you saying "not working" or "juststudying.uk" doesn't help. When we load the
                site it works perfectly fine. - Also add your email to it so we can contact you
                about it so we can fix the "issue"
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Small update</title>
            <link>/assets/img/change_log/update4.png</link>
            <description>Didn't add much here. working on some features behind the scene but they
                arent ready to be released at all.
                And can you guys beat my score. send it in Q&amp;A. added the pokemon game cuz
                somebody asked
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>I need a way to contact back</title>
            <link>/assets/img/change_log/email.png</link>
            <description>Can you guys please provide a way of contact. I want to be able to help but
                you guys just send one message and dont explain further. Add a email or something?
                Also dont forget your GCSE's if u from uk
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>GCSE Exams!</title>
            <link>
                https://www.tmc.ac.uk/media/filer_public_thumbnails/filer_public/ff/d8/ffd8f37f-0a66-4ada-844e-9e7bcabd80c3/gcse.png__564x307_subject_location-282%2C153_subsampling-2.webp</link>
            <description>We know everyone here loves playing JustStudy and to be honest focuses on
                playing games more than learning. Just remember for the Year 11's it's now GCSE
                week! All the exams are going to come at a fast pace. Use the revision lessons
                wisely and limit your time playing JustStudy! If you actually want to study there
                will be studying resources for English LIT+LANG, Maths, Combined SCI and more
                soon...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Bloons galore</title>
            <link>/assets/img/change_log/update3.png</link>
            <description>Apes against helium rubber balls. i like the bloon games so i decided to
                bundle most of the first and classic games. have fun! "might add bloons td5 but its
                very slow". Also added blockpost
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New Sorting type and more</title>
            <link>/assets/img/change_log/update2.png</link>
            <description><![CDATA[I have added a new sorting type... Popularity! This shows how much players went into the game in the past week.
            which resets each week. so maybe for example slope got popular one week then it reset and a different game got popular!
            I also updated the news. the old one was ugly so I did a little revamp. hope you guys like it! 
            ]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>